ih8mud.com 2012-10-22

# Legal and Privacy Policy :: Your Online Offroad Resource – IH8MUD.com

This legal statement discloses the practices for the websites and information hosted by Tie Rod Media LLC and located at http://www.ih8mud.com and http://www.rockcrawler.com and all related subdomains, including http://forum.ih8mud.com,  http://gallery.ih8mud.com, http://www.cruiserfaq.com, etc.

**Tie Rod Media LLC is organized as a Limited Liability Company under the laws of the State of Wisconsin.**

This website is for reference and entertainment purposes only. By the use of this site or by clicking any images, buttons or text links, you accept these terms and conditions and acknowledge that your use of IH8MUD.com or RockCrawler.com and its related sites is subject to the terms and conditions outlined as follows. Tie Rod Media LLC is in no way responsible or liable for any injuries or damages incurred because of the use of information provided or linked within these sites.

All content posted on IH8MUD.com/RockCrawler.com becomes the property of Tie Rod Media LLC (unless otherwise stated) based on copyright law and may not be duplicated elsewhere without written permission.

#### Notification of Changes

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter these terms and conditions at any time. Such modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof. You must review this agreement on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes. You can find the most recent version of the TOU at: <http://www.ih8mud.com/privacy/>

All corporate trademarks are the property of their respective owners and are used to refer to those specific products or activities related to those products. Tie Rod Media LLC’s use of these trademarks in its stories in no way infers that any relationship exists between Tie Rod Media LLC and the trademark owner.

#### Registration

In order to fully utilize all aspects of this website, users must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and valid email address). This information may be used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Demographic or other personal information is purely voluntary (such as occupation and vehicle). You agree not to use the message boards, membership list or email addresses contained herein as a way to gather data, request interviews, solicit, gather data, etc.

This information will never be sold or given away and Tie Rod Media LLC will take reasonable action to protect this information from outside entities. We will provide any and all information requested by law enforcement with proper documentation.

Freedom of Speech: Although the Constitution of the US guarantees that ‘Congress shall make no law abridging the freedom of speech’, Tie Rod Media LLC is not Congress. Freedom of speech rights do not extend to this privately owned website. The Legal/Privacy Guidelines of this website govern the behaviors and activities of the members and users. If you choose not to follow these guidelines, the result will be a disabling of your account.

#### Third Party Advertising

Tie Rod Media LLC relies on third-party ad servers and ad networks to serve advertisements. These third-party ad servers and ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear on the site and they automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. Such third-party ad servers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content.

Tie Rod Media LLC does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent, unless part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. Please note that if an advertiser asks Tie Rod Media LLC to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, males age 18 to 25) or audience segment (for example, males age 18 to 25 who have participated in certain community forums) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience that they were trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Tie Rod Media LLC Policies do not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Tie Rod Media LLC reserves the right the add or remove third-party ad networks or ad servers in its discretion and Tie Rod Media LLC may not at all times list such updated ad network or ad server partners in this Privacy Notice.

Currently, Tie Rod Media LLC has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks:

  * Google – http://www.google.com/privacy.html
  * VigLink - http://www.viglink.com/policies/privacy
  * EBay – https://publisher.ebaypartnernetwork.com/PublisherRegPP
  * ContextWeb/ADSDAQ – http://www.contextweb.com/ppolicy.html
  * Commission Junction – http://www.cj.com/privacy.html
  * TextLinkAds/MediaWhiz – http://www.mediawhiz.com/privacy-policy.html
  * Amazon – http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496
  * InfoLinks – http://www.infolinks.com/privacy.html
  * Kontera – http://www.kontera.com/kontera-privacy-policy
  * IntelliTXT – http://www.vibrantmedia.com/privacy.asp

#### Cookies

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information ( _e.g.,_ the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

#### Log Files

Tie Rod Media LLC uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate statistical use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Tie Rod Media LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This legal statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Surveys & Contests

Our website requests information from users via surveys and/or for contests. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. All information submitted must be correct or that person will be disqualified.

#### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Online, our security policy is that only those people who have a need to know have access to the database, and a security policy is in place to prevent any unauthorized people from using this database. If and when our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with encryption software. While on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Google Chrome and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. If and when we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please email us at our contact web page.

#### Children’s Online Privacy

If this web site pertains mainly to children under the age of 13, there will be a mechanism to collect age information and to obtain parental consent for the use of the website by the child. If parental consent is not granted, access to that child will be blocked, per (COPPA).

#### Special Offers

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we do offer a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing us at our contact web page, where we offer email, and possibly mail and/or telephone methods of contact.

#### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive email from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by changing it in their profile.

#### Liability

Any or all activities and/or actions depicted in this site may be hazardous, the authors of this material only relate their personal experiences. This website does not endorse or recommend any particular activity or action. Use common sense and discretion before engaging in any activity.

IH8MUD and RockCrawler provide a collection of online resources, including classified ads, forums, and various other services.  By using these service in any way, you are agreeing to comply with site policies. In addition, when using particular service, you agree to abide by any applicable posted guidelines for all services, which may change from time to time. Should you object to any term or condition, any guidelines, or any subsequent modifications thereto or become dissatisfied in any way, your only recourse is to immediately discontinue use of these sites. We reserve the right, but are not obligated, to strictly enforce site policies through self-help, community moderation, active investigation, litigation and prosecution.

Tie Rod Media LLC assumes no liability for your use of the material contained within this site.

#### Forum/Bulletin Board

Our Forum is visited by members of the general public. Tie Rod Media LLC is in no way liable for actions direct or indirect, caused by people’s posts and opionions.   You understand that all postings, messages, text, files, images, photos, video, sounds, or other materials (“Content”) posted on, transmitted through, or linked from IH8MUD/RockCrawler, are the sole responsibility of the person from whom such Content originated. More specifically, you are entirely responsible for each individual item (“Item”) of Content that you post, email or otherwise make available via the Service. You understand that IH8MUD/RockCrawler does not control, and is not responsible for Content made available, and that by using these sites, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent, inaccurate, misleading, or otherwise objectionable. Furthermore, IH8MUD/RockCrawler and Content available through the Service may contain links to other websites, which are completely independent. Tie Rod Media LLC makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of the information contained in any such site. Your linking to any other webites is at your own risk. You agree that you must evaluate, and bear all risks associated with, the use of any Content, that you may not rely on said Content, and that under no circumstances will Tie Rod Media LLC be liable in any way for any Content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed or otherwise made available. You acknowledge that Tie Rod Media LLC does not pre-screen or approve Content, but  shall have the right (but not the obligation) in its sole discretion to refuse, delete or move any Content that is available via the Service, for violating the letter or spirit of the policies or for any other reason.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or about your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  admin@ih8mud.com
